let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which river did not flow out of Eden?",
        answer: "Jordan",
        options: [
            "Euphrates", "Jordan", "Gihon", "Tigris"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question:  "According to the book of Nahum, where is the way of the Lord?",
        answer: "In whirlwind and storm",
        options: [
            "In the storm and wave", "In the sea", "In clouds", "In whirlwind and storm"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which was the 6th plague to strike Egypt?",
        answer: "Tumours",
        options: [
            "Locusts", "Tumours", "Heavy hail", "Frogs"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the name of the sister mentioned in the book of Philemon?",
        answer: "Apphia",
        options: [
            "Junia", "Apphia", "Prisca", "Stephanas"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "To whom did the Lord promise that he will be made into an iron pillar?",
        answer: "Jeremiah",
        options: [
            "Jeremiah", "Isaiah", "Ezekiel", "Peter"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What was NOT brought down from Tarshish by Solomon's ships every three years?",
        answer: "Horses",
        options: [
            "Silver", "Horses", "Apes", "Peacocks"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What were the cherubims on the mercy seat made of?",
        answer: "Gold",
        options: [
            "Wood", "Bronze", "Silver", "Gold"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How many pieces of silver did Judas get for delivering Jesus?",
        answer: "30",
        options: [
            "20", "30", "40", "50"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Who healed the man with the withered hand?",
        answer: "Jesus",
        options: [
            "Peter", "Paul", "John", "Jesus"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "`The wind bloweth where it listeth,` said Jesus to ?",
        answer: "Nicodemus",
        options: [
            "Nicodemus", "Peter", "Zacchaeus", "Pharisees"
        ]
    }
];
